[i]CNN News Anchor:[/i] Rami spots his neighbor,
Abu Ahmad.
Something's not right.
[i]Rami:[/i] What's going on Abu Ahmad?
What's wrong?
It's all in Gods hands...
[i]Abu:[/i] My son, Ahmad!
[i]Rami:[/i] It's all in Gods hands...
It's all in Gods hands...
It's all in Gods hands -
[i]Abu:[/i] I told you
let's stay at home
my son!
I told him,
let's stay at home!
[i]Rami:[/i] Let's carry him.
Let's carry him.
[i]Abu:[/i] I told you,
let's stay at home, my son!
[i]Rami:[/i] Let's go. Let's go.
[Abu waves a white flag.]
[He was carrying it when a sniper shot his son.]
[i]Abu:[/i] If only
we had stayed at home,
God!
Ahmad? Ahmad!
Are you breathing my son?
[i]Rami:[/i] Yes, he is breathing.
He is breathing.
Breathing? Let's carry him.
Yes, yes.
Carry him. Carry him.
Pray to god.
He is still alive.
There is breathing.
[i]News anchor:[/i] Ahmad was shot in the head.
He didn't make it.