[i]Palestinian reporter[/i] ... The doctors were shocked that
this woman's wound was bleeding,
which meant
that she was not able to get
any treatment
or medical support.
They told me there are
many similar cases.
They told me about a woman
whose arm was amputated.
She had surgery on her arm.
But, she was the only survivor
from her family
with her young daughter.
So, she left Al-Shifa hospital,
with one amputated arm,
and the other arm
holding her daughter.
And when she reached here -
[voice breaking]
her situation was very dire.
We witnessed today
so many difficult injuries.
so many difficult cases.
The situation is getting worse
in an indescribable way.
Yes, we are talking about thousands of martyrs,
But we are also talking about
the numerous humanitarian cases.
Entire families have made it to the south,
Holding their wounded
and amputated children and women
We have witnessed cases
that are hard to describe.
The doctors and medical teams were talking about
very serious injuries.
They talked about entire families suffering.
We witnessed unbearable humanitarian cases
today and yesterday.
We witnessed the emptying of the hospitals
of the wounded,
of the martyrs' families
who had to leave their childrens' corpses behind.
An elderly man told us
that he had to leave his daughter -
wounded.
He does not know if she made it or not.
But he had to save the rest of his family
and leave the hospital.
He had to choose to sacrifice one daughter,
so he does not sacrifice his entire family.
This is what the humanitarian situation
has become now in Gaza.
This is what the scene has become in Gaza.
This is what the entire world
is watching.
All that we can say now,
when talking about
the situation
in Al-Shifa hospital,
is that there is constant bombardment,
and the medical teams
are trying to support the patients
and the displaced,
and how they feel the responsibility to keep working
inside the hospital, despite everything.