[i]Blinken:[/i] - not, shrinking back.
not in the face of Russia's aggression against Ukraine.
not, in the face of-
[i]Protestor:[/i] Stop this brutal massacre in Gaza!
The U.S. is supporting a brutal massacre!
[i]Coordinator:[/i] if the witness will suspend -
[i]Protestor:[/i] 66% of Americans say they want a ceasefire!
And yet, not one senator
is calling for a ceasefire!
Shame on you all!
The world is calling for a ceasefire!
The American people don't want to support -
[Security attempts to remove the protestor]
this brutal war!
Stop the war!
Stop the - [stumbles]
Ceasefire now!
Stop funding this brutal massacre!
That Israel is doing on the people of Gaza!
Ceasefire now!
[i]Coordinator:[/i] Thank you Senator Blinken, if you can continue.