Since the seventh of October,
we face extermination,
killing,
bombing falling over our heads,
all -
all of this in front of the world.
They lie to the world that they kill [?]
but they
kill the people of Gaza,
their dreams and their future.
Kids of Gaza run out of their [?]
We come to Al-Shifa hospital
to keep us from bombing.
We suddenly run out of [into?] more.
After bombing the hospital,
the occupation is starving us.
We don't find water, food,
and we drink from the unusable water.
We come now to shout,
and invite you to protect us.
We want to live! We want peace!
We want to [?] have shelter!
We want medicine, food, and education!
And we want to live as the other children live.