[i]Fadi Abu Shamallah:[/i] I start from, from the heavy airstrike
and the shelling over all of Gaza Strip
every single minute that we have been bombed.
The numbers talked about,
10,000 rockets have been launched over Gaza Strip.
More than 12,000
of civilian people have been killed.
Hundreds of people, civilian people,
are still under rubbles,
and [inaudible]
are not able to rescue them
and pull them out from under the rubbles.
Or should I talk about the
entire neighborhoods that’s flattened,
the road that is cut off,
the water,
the severe shortage of water,
the severe shortage of food, fuel?
We don’t have electricity
for more than 20 days now or more.
I don’t know, to talk about the UNRWA shelters,
that it has around more than
half-million of displaced people.
Israel asked us to evacuate
the Gaza City and the north,
because in there -
and they killed, they assassinated,
they targeted the convoy of cars
while they were traveling
and evacuating to the south of Gaza Strip.
Should I talk about the live video
that’s recorded by
and broadcasted by a journalist,
Palestinian local journalist?
His name is Hassan Saifi.
He filmed and recorded a video
while the tank launched and bombed a civilian car
while they were evacuating
to the south.
What should I talk about?
That we don’t have bread?
That we don’t have water?
We don’t have fuel.
Nothing.
We have only one thing:
that we are being killed.
There is -
and, of course,
with a green light with the international community,
with the U.S. administration.
This is the situation.
People are scared.
From what? For being killed.
Really, we are having now
a second Nakba, if you know it.
The first one happened in 1948.
We feel that it’s another Nakba
that we are going through,
to go through it.
The most horrible thing for us,
that’s the officials.
The Israeli officials say
that we are human animals.
Human animals? Animal humans?
I don’t remember exactly.
Like, we are treated like animals.
You know what happen to animals?
They’re slaughtered.
So, we are slaughtered now
by the Israeli genocide government.
This is what’s happening now.
Like, they now [inaudible].
This is what is going on here,
a genocide.
A real genocide and massacre
is happening now.
Like, in previous wars, we used to have
like 10 persons of a family is killed.
Now,
the whole building,
the entire neighborhoods is bombed,
flattened.
It’s happening in Jabaliya for three days,
in Nuseirat,
in Khan Younis city,
in every single mid-Gaza Strip cities.
This is what is happening here now.
I’m a father of three kids,
as you have mentioned.
They think that I’m a hero.
I’m not.
I’m scared exactly like them.