[i]Girl under rubble:[/i] Get me out of here, please!
[i]Man:[/i] We will rescue you!
[i]Girl:[/i] Please, get me out of here
[i]Man:[/i] Do you have a phone to light up?
[i]Girl:[/i] No, I'm here, I can't move
I see a light near me
[i]Man:[/i] Is there wood above you?
[i]Girl:[/i] I don't know, there's... I can't
[i]Man:[/i] I bear witness that there is no god but Allah.
[i]Man:[/i] and Muhammad is the Prophet of God.
[i]Man:[/i] Just a moment
[i]Girl:[/i] Why is this happening to us?
Man: Say Allah,
first thing, say Allah,
first thing say Allah -
is this your hand?
Good
[i]Man:[/i] There is... Is there anyone with you?
Is there anyone else here?
Just a moment
I'm here talking to her
[Girl moans in pain]
I'm here talking to her.
I'm here talking to her. Just a moment -
Are you laying your legs or not
So we know where to dig
Are your legs still layed?
[i]Girl:[/i] Hurry up please
[i]Man:[/i] Oh God.
[i]Girl:[/i] I cannot breathe
[i]Man:[/i] Say Allah, say Allah.
[i]Girl:[/i] [weakly] I bear witness that there is no God but Allah.
[i]Man:[/i] I bear witness that there is no God but Allah.
[i]Man:[/i] We are about to get you. We are about to get you.