[i]Dr. Mads Gilbert:[/i] I'm a medical doctor. I'm a civilian.
I have been all around in Shifa hospital
for 16 years.
I've been walking freely everywhere.
I've taken pictures and videos.
I've talked to anybody, to patients, and to staff.
I've even been sleeping in the Shifa hospital
and I have never seen any signs
of any military command center in Shifa.
But I think, again, you have to ask the Israelis
because if they are so sure
about this... "command center"
that they have been talking about
for sixteen years now
where is the proof?
Where are the pictures?
Where is the... The x-ray, of the hospital?
Because,
you have to remember that Israel has a very
sophisticated intelligence.
And they have been x-raying
the ground of Gaza.
They have mapped all the tunnels for the resistance.
They know the phone number of every citizen.
They know the addresses.
They know exactly who lives where.
So why is it that this...
"Brilliant"...
Israeli intelligence system
has not been able to put forward any proof?
These are all the lies of war.
Israel is a...
A chronicle -
A chronic liar.
Any normal human being
with a heart
would not attack hospitals.
Israel has a long history of attacking hospitals
and ambulances...
Health personnel...
Primary healthcare clinics...
And they have done that since I first was in Gaza
during bombing in 2006.
So, in this situation would any sensible
person... General...
Prime Minister... With a heart, would say,
"We will have ceasfire. We will take care of the wounded.
We will re-establish the function of the hospitals."
What is Israel doing?
They are increasing the bombing.
Increasing the number of wounded.
Increasing the siege of the hospitals.
And the strangulation of the people.
So if you are not killed during the Israeli bombing,
they want to starve you,
to thirst you,
to bleed you,
and scare you to death.
So to me, this is, you know,
it's not only war crimes.
This is - this is crimes against humanity.
And this is crimes against the value base
that we all should have.
If we are muslims,
or christians,
or jews,
or... agnostics.
That every. Human. Life. Is. Sacred.
And that we should save and protect every human life.
In Gaza,
Lives are shred like this. [Makes tearing gesture with hands]
And the European leaders,
And this... "President" Joe Biden,
Is... Completely silent,
or, even worse,
they are supporting the Israeli atrocities.
I think the Palestinian people today
is the only people on earth
to have to prove that they are killed.
They have to prove that they are dead.
Because Joe Biden says that he doubts the numbers,
from the Minister of Health in Gaza.
And I say to you all,
Stand up for Palestine,
stand up for Gaza,
we are all Gaza.
Now we need solidarity more than ever,
that's much more important than
what a Norwegian doctor can do.
We need now to be strong
And to say to the leaders and to the world,
That we don't accept this.