Man 1: Who are you looking for?
Man 2: My four children
My four children.
Oh god.
Man 1: May God reward you.
Man 2: Oh my beloved God...
I wish I died instead.
Man 1: They went ahead of you to heaven.
Man 2: What did they do!! My dears...
[Crying] What did they do?
[Sobbing]
Man 1: They are in heaven, my dear,
In paradise, my beloved, in paradise,
They preceded you.
There is no God but Allah.
Man 2: My children!
I can't hear you...
[Man's foot shifts metal rubble]
[Rubble shifts as man digs]
Man 2: Salma! [His daughter's name]
Salma!
Salma, my beloved!
Saied! [His son's name]
[Digging at rubble]
Saied!
Son!
Didn't I tell you
take care of our house
take care of your sister...
Didn't I say take care of our family, my son...
[Crying]