[i]Palestinian reporter:[/i] This is how things looks inside
the emergency department at Al-Shifa hospital.
The department is full of the injured.
Here, we enter the critical cases department.
The patients are too much that
they are being treated on the floor.
They are dying because of the collapse of the health care system,
the lack of medicine,
and Israel's siege on hospitals.
The scene is too horrible to describe.
The injured of Gaza are left alone by the world
facing Israel's bombardment of hospitals.
The medical staff were also martyred,
injured,
and displaced.
It's not clean here,
the floor is full of blood.
Medical crews are helpless
because of the massive number of the injuries.
This child has died because of the lack of healthcare.
His brother is probably dying
The man is putting the child who was killed
in the bombardment of the outpatient clinics
in Al-Shifa hospital next to his brother.
This is how it looks here.
Even the hospitals have been bombed.
The displaced children who thought
that hospitals are save were killed
inside the hospitals.
Dead bodies remain on the floor.
Journalists left the hospital
because of the hard situation and insecurity.
The courtyard was bombed too
by the Israeli occupation
The treatment here is barbaric and inhuma.
This has never happened in any time.
I don't think anyone has dared to target hospitals, clinics
or children blood,
except those who are internationally supported
and use the excuse of "self defense" to kill children