[i]Rozan Al-Rifi[/i]: What do I even say?
Supposedly, Israel
is a democratic
and diplomatic state?
Where is the democracy?
My father was martyred.
My mother was martyred.
My brother was martyred.
My nephew was martyred.
And my sister was martyred.
My brother was a newly-wed.
We are exhausted!
We are exhausted.
My brother is so young!
A child!
Allah will call them to account.
My siblings are wounded.
We are so exhausted.
Why can't you feel for us?
Everyone left us behind.
[i]Cameraman: Where are you from?[/i]
[i]Rozan[/i]: We are from the Northeast.
[i]Cameraman:[/i] From Gaza city?
[i]Rozan:[/i] Yes, from Al-Tuffah neighborhood.
[i]Cameraman[/i]: Which family?
[i]Rozan:[/i] Al-Rifi.
[i]Cameraman:[/i] What's your name?
[i]Rozan:[/i] Rozan Ahmad Al-Rifi.
My father was martyred
at 3AM in the morning.
And my mother -
and my siblings.