[i]Ta-nehisi Coates:[/i] You can't behold evil,
and then return and not speak on it.
And, segregation is evil.
There just is no, there is no way for me,
as an African American,
to come back, and stand before you,
to witness segregation,
and not say anything about it.
One of the hardest things,
ah...
was to come back,
and then to read the rhetoric
of certain African American politicians,
who... are defending this regime!
And I just - I - I - I couldn't understand it!
You know - I wanted to know if they had been to Hebron!
You know - I - I wanted to know,
if they had been to Masafer Yatta,
If they had been to Susiya,
if they had been to Tuba,
had - had they seen!?
Had they really seen,
what is actually
happening here?
I - I - I don't know how anybody
who benefits, who stands on the shoulders
of our ancestors' struggle,
against Jim Crow,
against segregation,
could see what is happening right now -
could see the bombs being dropped,
nine thousand people dead,
an ungodly number of them, children,
in service of Jim Crow,
and segregation -
which we have exported -
and be okay with that.
I - I don't - I don't understand.
So yes, I have my fears, I do, I do.
You know, I'm afraid right now,
sitting here talking to you.
but I have to measure my fear,
against the misery,
that I saw.
I have to measure my fear
against the promises
that I made,
to the Palestinians who welcomed me
into their homes
and gave me the facts.
To the Israeli Jews
who welcomed me into their homes,
and gave me the facts.
To the Holocaust survivors
who welcomed me into their homes,
and gave me the facts.
I have to measure it against my own ancestors,
against Fredrick Douglass,
against Ida B. Wells,
who certainly faced off against things
that were much, much more perilous
than...
going someplace,
coming back
and telling people what you saw.
This is the minimum!
It’s scary,
but it’s also the minimum.
And the fact that people are trying to suppress...
speech..
is not an excuse for you not to speak.
It’s always been this way for black writers and journalists.
This is our tradition, you know?
And so, I feel — as I do feel the fear,
I also feel that I am in good company,
because I’m in the company of my ancestors.