We sought refuge here thinking it was a safe haven.
Our last safe haven,
in a church.
The house of God.
Those are...
My three children.
I lost them to the Israeli aggression against Gaza
During the air strike to the Church of Saint Porphyrius.
Suhail Ramez El Soury,
Jouly Ramez El Soury,
Majd Ramez El Soury,
This is the place that was bombed.
It was an all-civilian place.
It had nothing to do with the military.
This photo was taken during Palm Sunday.
This is Majd, my little bird. Look at him.
He was a child.
He became disfigured.
He became dead and disfigured.
His stomach was burned and had shrapnel.
My daughter Sima as well.
Her head was crushed.
She was disfigured. My daughter Sima.
I myself pulled Suhail's body from the rubble.
He was hit in his head and feet, which were almost cut off.
Sima is now a beautiful bride next to God.
She is... She was an angel.
An angel.
She is an angel. She is an angel.
Do they bomb angels?
They bombed my angels and killed them without warning.
They killed our children, the children of cousins and relatives.
[Crying]
This is what they targeted. This was our shelter.
This was our church.
This was the entrance.
We used to enter from here to pray to celebrate our joy.
Stay Strong.
They took my children from me.