Podcast host: On Wednesday,
our colleague, Wael Al-Dadouh,
lost several members of his family
to an Israeli airstrike.
He was live on air as it landed.
[Distorted sound of a jet passing overhead]
[Rattling of objects]
Female translator: It's clear there is a new strike on Gaza
close to Wael Al-Dadouh.
Wael,
tell us what's happening.
Male translator: yes, Laila, I can hear you.
Podcast host: And he was live on air
when he learned it killed his family.
And in the hospital, where he saw them.
[Anguished man speaking Arabic]
Male translator: He's gone?
They take revenge by killing our children.
It's okay.
We belong to God, and to him, we shall return.
Podcast host: They were in central Gaza,
where Israel had told people in the north to go
to avoid airstrikes.
Some of his family members survived,
some are still buried in the rubble.
His wife, his son, his daughter, his grandson...
and members of his extended family, were killed.