We can't take it anymore, we're exhausted.
Here, we become martyred victims.
In a matter of time,
we are going one after another.
No one is seeing us
or the size of this catastrophe
and the crime we are experiencing in Gaza.
[Reporter on air crying]
No international security at all,
no immunity or anything at all,
for these shields or these helmets.
These are merely slogans that we wear and that is all.
They don't protect any journalists at all.
[Taking off press vest] These shields don't protect us
they are merely slogans.
[Taking off helmet] We are losing souls,
one after another.
We are victims, directly on live television.
We are losing souls one after the other,
with complete immunity.
We are martyred victims in a matter of time,
we wait our turn, one after the other.
Our colleague, Mohammed Abu Hatab was here,
just half an hour ago
and now he has left us.
Along with his wife, and son, and brother
and many other victims from his family,
here inside the hospital.