This was an act of sheer evil.
More than one thousand civilians slaughtered.
Not just killed - slaughtered.
In Israel.
Among them, at least fourteen American citizens killed.
Parents butchered using their bodies to try to protect their children.
Stomach-turning reports of being — babies being killed.
Entire families slain.
Young people massacred while attending a musical festival to celebrate peace -
to celebrate peace.
Women raped, assaulted, paraded as trophies.
Families...
hid their fear for hours and hours
desperately trying to keep their children quiet
to avoid drawing attention.
And thousands of wounded,
alive but carrying with them the bullet holes, the shrapnel wounds, and the memory
of what they endured.
You all know these traumas never go away.
There are still so many families desperately waiting to hear the fate of their loved ones,
not knowing if they’re alive or dead or hostages.
Infants in their mothers’ arms, grandparents in wheelchairs,
Holocaust survivors abducted and held hostage -
hostages whom Hamas has now threatened to execute
in violation of every code of human morality.
It’s abhorrent.
The brutality of Hamas -
this bloodthirstiness -
rings to mind the worst — the worst rampages of ISIS.
This is terrorism.
But sadly, for the Jewish people, it’s not new.
This attack has brought to the surface painful memories
and the scars left by a millennia of antisemitism and genocide of the Jewish people.
So, in this moment,
we must be crystal clear:
We stand with Israel.