[i]CNN anchor Wolf Blitzer:[/i] Back down to our breaking news
here in the middle east.
A massive explosion
at the largest refugee camp
in Gaza.
Joining us now is Lieutenant Colonel Richard Hecht.
He is the international spokesperson
for the Israel Defense Forces.
Thanks so much for joining us.
I wanna ask you first about this
massive blast
that we all just saw - we saw the video -
at the Jabaliya refugee camp in Gaza.
Is there anything more you can,
first of all, tell us
about how this explosion happened?
[i]Richard:[/i] Hi Wolf, thanks for having me. So,
We'll be coming out, in the next,
hopefully, hour,
with more data, but I can update you
now that there was a very senior
Hamas commander in that area,
sadly he was hiding, again,
as they do,
behind, eh, behind civilians,
and that's all I can say at this point.
We'll be looking into it and we'll be
coming out with more data as we learn what happened here.
[i]Wolf:[/i] So can you confirm it was an Israeli attack
that- that destroyed a big chunk
of that Jabaliya refugee camp?
[i]Richard:[/i] Yes I can.
We were focused again on the target, a senior -
a senior commander, Wolf,
and we'll be updating you
with more data as the hour moves ahead.
[i]Wolf:[/i] But even if that, uh, Hamas commander
was there admist all those Palestinian refugees
who were in that Jabaliya refugee camp
Israel still went ahead and dropped a bomb there,
attempting to kill this Hamas commander,
knowing that a lot of innocent civilians -
men, women, and children -
presumably, would be killed - is that what I'm hearing?
[i]Richard:[/i] That's not what you're hearing, Wolf.
We, again, were focused on this commander.
again, you'll get more data on who this man was,
killed many, many Israelis,
we're doing everything we can, this is a very complicated
battle space. There could be infrastructure there.
There could be tunnels there.
We're still looking into it
and we'll give you more data as the hour moves ahead.
[i]Wolf:[/i] But you know that there are a lot of refugees -
a lot of innocent civilians -
men, women, and children -
in that refugee camp as well, right?
[i]Richard:[/i] This is the tragedy of war, Wolf.
As you know, we've been saying for days.
Move south.
Civilians who are not involved with Hamas,
please move south.
We, uh -
[i]Wolf:[/i] Just trying to get a little more information.
You knew there were civilians there.
You knew there were refugees.
All sorts of refugees.
But you decided to still drop a bomb
on that refugee camp, attempting
to kill this Hamas commander -
by the way, was he killed?
[i]Richard:[/i] I can't confirm yet, there'll be more, uh, updated -
he, yes, we know that he was killed.
About the civilians there,
we're doing everything we can to minimize.
I'll say it again:
sadly, they are hiding themselves within
civilian populations.
And again, we're doing this stage by stage,
and we're gonna go after every one of these terrorists
involved on that henious attack on the 7th of October, Wolf.